coming up: finals week
monday
good morning :)
rainy day
so cozy and i love the sound of rain!
perfect time to start my day with some coffee
cold drinks on a cold day
it looks so delicious
mix mix mix
i'm in n my pink era
starting my day with some planning!
i've been using scrintal a lot recently and i'm so excited to introduce scrintal to you
scrintal works as a visual note taking and mind mapping tool,
using scrintal, you can freely brainstorm ideas, present findings, plan and so much more
your own whiteboard where you can visually organize and group all your thoughts and ideas together
really love how simple and minimalistic it is which makes it so much easier to understand
you can use scrintal for anything wether it's school, work or your personal life
scrintal has helped me so much through this hectic week, so this is something i highly recommend
create digital calender and edit them however you want, font, color and layout
i like to change the colors to make it more alive but also more organized
scrintal has been very helpful with my school work, but i also like to plan my everyday life
you can brainstorm and put all your ideas in here, use scrintal however you like :)
scrintal offers the perfect solution for balancing linear and visual thinking
use hashtags to type out the subject of your card
so that you can find everything in a pop up list which displays all the names of your cards
scrintal's canvas features allows users to visualize eac idea seperately and draw connections effortlessly
bringing two worlds together both visually and text based
connect different cards together and easily navigate from one idea to another
more about scrintal and how i used scrintal through my finals week will be explained throughout this video so stay tuned!
time to start working
i really like these new heart shaped pens i got recently!
i hope all of you are doing good and enjoying your summer break :)
if you have work to do then feel free to study along with me!
i'm trying my best to stay focused this week and putting all my energy into these exams,
i tried my best to get as much footage as possible this week,
but i had to do a lot of work off camera since it was a bit distracting, hope you understand
study with me
i wasn't kidding when i said i was in my pink era lol
my hand is already tired..
highlighting my notes as the last step
i'm going to start taking notes on my ipad instead
for some reason my hands hurt more when i write on paper
i attempted to make my own this time, what do you think?
it doesn't look that good but at least it was delicious
took a little break to clean my room
even though i would like to take my short breaks to resting or do something fun,
i just can't ignore the fact that my room is messy
a clean environment is so important to stay focused :)
my rooms feel so empty, i'm thinking of buying some plants
asked my dad to pick up an energy drink on his way home
struggling..
let's pretend i opened it with one hand
i've felt super motivated lately to study korean
it's always fun but i'm just more excited to studying it now,
because there might be a time soon when my poor korean skills will be in use... (hint)
learning basic conversations and also going through a few flashcards
i took a nap then spent the rest of my night studying..
tuesday
at a cafe
what i ordered
came here early to get some work done
this is probably my favorite cafe to study at, it's so peaceful and the music here is so relaxing
1 sugar isn't enough
i love studying at cafe's
i feel so motivated seeing other people work hard around me
i always forget to drink/eat when i'm focused
i'm the worst at multitasking
this bread/dessert was a bit dry :/
my dad didn't want it so i had to eat it myself lol
got some work done yay
ok let's get back home now
but first finish my coffe that got cold..
" it wasn't that good..."
the view back home is so pretty
i don't even want to go back gome
package from doogee
doogee was kind enough to send me one of their tablets once again for me to unbox :)
i was truly shocked last time about how great the quality was so i'm very excited!
this is the t30 mac, 12.4 inch 4k ultra sensory color screen, featuring a large screen with super high display effiency
they even sent me one of their pens!!
what i like about the company is that you get such high quality products for a very good price
the tablet with large screen is under $350 which is amazing!
i really love the pencil design